hey what are you doing here oh come on
in I'm Brett contas and welcome to
personal trainer cribs episode one so
I'm really excited about my new condo
and I want to show it off it won't take
too long because it's pretty small but
I'm just going to start from here and
work my way uh back into into the place
this here is my
bathroom just your your general bathroom
here nothing too special but uh this
here this is my my shaver I cut my own
hair So eventually I I will get a barber
one day and I'll look respectable but
until then I'm I'm happy to cut my own
uh let's see here um if you notice here
I've got an iron gym for Pull-Ups I'm
6'4 um so I was a little bit worried
because I thought that maybe I'd be uh
you know have to do partials but I can
just make it so I can start from my
knees just like that come up all the
way
so ends up being perfect I can do full
range chin-ups there um okay moving
along uh this here is my fan and I
really like this because I I just like
it for the white noise so every night
before I go to sleep I will turn this
on and
uh I just leave it on for the white
noise that way I don't get woken up by
cars or dogs that are barking I just
like the uh you know it blocks out the
ambient noise um all right before you
come into my bedroom you need to
understand that I'm single I don't have
a girlfriend I'm sure if I if I did have
a girlfriend she'd throw a tantrum over
this but um I don't have to worry about
that right now so I
I smuggled my my glute ham rays and my
lever Squat and some other equipment so
um here I've
got this is a a 48 kg kettle bell and uh
so this is so this weighs 106 lb so I've
got the kettle bell here to do kettle
bell swings which is
nice and
uh I use that for a different things
I'll do like uh goblet squats swings one
arm rows things like
that here is my my glute ham raise
machine and uh this is from Elite FTS I
do back extensions glute ham raises
single leg back extensions and um this
is cool cuz it's got the little hook so
I can do these with band resistance or I
can just hold on to a dumbbell and use
dumbbell resistance and then here's my
lever Squat and I will do
like you know like full squats or
um uh reverse lunges and things like
that off this so I can get a really good
workout here um I also have you know
push-up
handles um 50b dumbbells and a bunch of
different bands um big bands smaller
bands I've got JC bands and uh I'll hook
the JC bands like around around one of
these band pegs and I'll I'll open this
door and I'll just do my presses and
things like that I'll get a really good
workout so um I also have a gym on the
third floor here which I'll show you a
little bit but uh here's my bed this is
a California KingSize bed so it's uh you
know big enough to accommodate me which
I like I'd like to say this is where the
magic happens but there's no magic going
on right now so I'm not going to lie to
you um but here are some things I really
like um
here I've got this LED light so at night
I'll just point that right where you
know at my book it's a pretty cool I I'm
amused by these little things in life um
before I go to sleep I try and read um
for instance right now I'm reading the
the mechanics of sprinting by by Ralph
man and then I'll also I'll try and have
a book that I'm reading and I'll also
have you know like a a journal article
that I try and read every night tonight
I'm going to read overtraining syndrome
this is a new uh um you know a brand new
study that came out so uh on
overtraining syndrome so I've always got
plenty of stuff to read now this is my
closet and it's really messy so cut me
some slack I just moved in here but the
reason I want to show you this is
because uh if you notice here my I've
just got so much reading material you
know if you go through my books I've got
you know Dan John Mark Wan I've got
Classics like Bron super squats dinosaur
training you know strongest shell
survive so um I've got all the all the
classics but I've also you know I have
uh textbooks on biomechanics I've got
DVDs by strength coaches here's Mike
Bo's uh functional strength coach 3.0
I've got Charlie wiro a few by uh Nick
tum manella a few by Dan John you know
I've got Elite FTS
um DVDs showing you know their their
Squat and deadlift and their bench press
exercises I've got you know cresy and
Robertson's magnificent Mobility I've
got paresi combine I've just you know
Glenn penl Olympic weightlifting um
Power by Smitty and Joe de Franco um you
know uh here I've got a bunch of
different uh you know textbooks on
biomechanics and and and different
things but I've also have you know like
here's AR
modern encyclopedia
Endocrinology um here's great cook
athletic Body and Balance um easy
strength by Dan John and pavle um Jim
Kil baso ultimate speed and and Agility
here's the new strength and conditioning
book by Marco Cardell this is a you know
very research based um Olympic
weightlifting book super training by Mel
SI science and practice of strength
training by zat zorski I've got movement
great Cook's new book U Mike Bo's new
book advances and functional training
this here is kind of funny this is uh
this is a book I got like I don't even
know like 1997 or something like that or
n uh This Is The Complete Book of butt
and legs which is funny because you know
it goes through and has all these
different butt
exercises um and uh you know oh this is
funny single leg pelvic lifts so here
we've got this guy in spandex doing
single leg glute Bridges um but you know
I read this so many years ago and I who
would have known
that years later I'd write my own book
on
glutes um
but as as you can see I'm always reading
I'm always learning I've got plenty of
stuff to learn not only research and and
and textbooks and you know technical
books but also practical books and
things you know things written by the
the world's best practitioners and the
best researchers so I surround myself
with with knowledge I also surround
myself with Fitness stuff I'm all you
know I have tons of equipment here I'll
also show you my gym but um that's what
I want to impress upon you if you want
to have a uh you know be fit you've got
to have a fit lifestyle if you want to
be a good rider in the field you've got
to you know you've got to obtain the
knowledge okay moving out to my
balcony this is kind of cool because I I
live in uh the builtmore area in Phoenix
it's a nice area it's on Camel Back In
24th Street and uh I've got a movie
theater literally right down the street
um right down this street is a movie
theater I really like this balcony
because down here I've got all these
palm trees it just makes me feel
tropical puts me in a good place
um this going be the living room and uh
here I've got
a an Ikea poster this is kind of cheap
but it's really awesome I love this I
love this picture here this puts me in a
good place too now a lot of this stuff I
I was expecting to come here and have to
spend a lot more money but I got a lot
of this stuff for really cheap like got
some of this stuff off Craigslist and
Ikea stuff like that but I got this
chair it's really comfortable this couch
you know a rug the table Wireless I got
a 60-in plasma TV um this is CSI going
right now and I I always have something
going on in the background it makes me
feel good I'll be working I'm not even
really watching the TV but I've got this
plane in the background which is nice um
what I really like is this is just this
giant window here so I you know during
the day I have a lot of sun coming in um
and at night I just like that I can see
you know a lot of the city and the
streets and the palm trees there
um I've also got my plant that I'm
destined to keep alive here's my
kitchen um got a scale here I try and
weigh myself every day right now I'm
weighing in at about like 218 which is
pretty light for me um I make eggs once
or twice a day here's my coffee maker
here's my shaker cup um as you can see
up here I've got my Biotest supplements
um I I drink like 10 scoops of whey
protein powder a day and about 10 caps
of fish oil a day so I'm really big on
whey protein and fish o just cuz it's so
quick and convenient but I also have
uh you know as for food I got some
veggies up here some orange juice milk
eggs ham cheese I've got some extra dark
chocolate there yogurt some Greek yogurt
um have some beer down there Negra
Modello their Shock Top wine in case I
ever brought a grill over but that's
that's just not happening these days and
uh and then here's my rule everyone who
comes over can have as much Diet Cherry
Doctor Pepper they want but they've got
to replace it so you've got to come up
here and anytime you take one out you've
got to place one back in there this way
I always have cold dietary Dr
Pepper um cabinet sunflower seeds olive
oil
peanuts tons of these These Are cashews
almonds and macadamia nuts some dried
cherries not much but uh anyway I've
I've showed you my place I hope you
liked it it's been fun but now it's time
for you to leave so you got to get the F
out so this is the third floor of my my
condo as you can see we've got drinking
fountains and here's this four
stationary bikes and and as we come over
here I've got a scale right
here and then
uh this is kind of cool cuz here's the
men's locker room this is pretty sweet
for just a condom
um don't worry there's no one in here
but
uh this here is a a SAA it's a steam
room so uh now I've got my
own my own steam room here which which I
use a few times a week
um back here we've got
showers which is pretty cool
um and then over
here hanging leg rise a a Roman chair
for leg raises and dip handles right
here got an app ma sheine pe deck and
reverse P deck um bunch of cardio
equipment over here treadmills
ellipticals um Step Mills but what's
really cool is that uh you know if you
were doing cardio you can be watching
the plasma over here so you can be
watching
TV adductor abductor machine leg
extension leg curl bunch of dumbbells
Swiss balls bench just adjustable bench
sit up pinch over here we've got an AB
wheel this here is a seated row machine
and a lap pull down this is a an
adjustable um military incline and bench
press and then this here is a seated leg
Crest so you know you can get a decent
workout here and just good for a change
of
scenery so this is just coming out of my
elevator on the rooftop um I've got a
pool here and a Jacuzzi here on the
rooftop so this is the 15th
floor and uh here I've got a heated
pool
um and then here I've got a jacuzzi and
I use this every single night on coming
to the jacuzzi and this overlooks the
City of Phoenix so um got some bathrooms
over there you know drinking fountain
and then uh
here uh you know this just overlooks the
city
so you know you've got the City of
Phoenix over there here's the Filmore
area right over
here um bunch of different stores
Cheesecake Factory Macy stuff like that
over here is a movie center and uh nice
building across the street so makes for
some really good scenery
this here is a parking garage uh
directly across the street from my condo
literally like 30 ft away from it and
I'll come up here with my brother and
we'll we'll do like interval Sprints for
like 30 minutes just walking and running
and sprinting and it's pretty nice cuz
sometimes we'll go up the ramps and
stuff like that um and then
uh this is also up here on the the
rooftop I've got a grill right here so I
try and barbecue once a week I'll make
hamburgers and brw worst and stuff like
that but it's a nice Grill that's easy
to use and then come around
here so this is a nice little setting
tables um so you can you know eat eat up
here and socialize but it overlooks the
city um City of
Phoenix right down here is Camel Back
Road um so again this is my place um I
I'm so happy living here it's uh I'm
really content right now this is like
heaven on Earth couldn't ask for
anything more right now hope you enjoyed
the video